<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on My Website</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Analysis Project</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Analyzing the Effect of Carbon Dioxide Emissions On Population Statistics Across World Regions Introduction For this exploratory data analysis project, I chose two datasets from the World Bank Indicators portal. I am interested in analyzing the disparities in important population estimates across world regions such as population size, life expectancy, and gross domestic product per capita. I also want to analyze the effect of CO2 emissions on human populations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling, Testing, and Predicting the Effect of Carbon Dioxide Emissions On Population Statistics Across World Regions Introduction For modeling, testing, and predicting project, I chose the dataset I previously created from two datasets from the World Bank Indicators portal. The &#39;nations&#39; dataset contains population statistics across several years for various countries using their three letter country codes. The variables include: &#39;iso2c&#39;, the two letter code for each country; &#39;iso3c&#39;, the three letter code for each country; &#39;country&#39;, the country name; &#39;year&#39;; &#39;gdp_percap&#39;, the gross domestic product per capita in current international dollars corrected for purchasing power in different territories; &#39;life_expect&#39;, the life expectancy at birth in years; &#39;population&#39;, the estimated total population at mid-year including all residents except refugees; &#39;birth_rate&#39;, the number of live births per 1,000 people based on the &#39;population&#39; estimate; &#39;neonat_mortal_rate&#39;, the number of babies dying before 28 days old per 1,000 live births that year; &#39;region&#39;, world boundaries set for administrative purposes by the World Bank; and &#39;income&#39;, four income groupings: low, lower-middle, upper-middle, and high.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
